<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Daily Pratchett</title>
    <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
    <description>A quote from Sir Terry Pratchett every day.</description>
    <atom:link href="http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/website/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>7/13/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29914</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:58:25 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29914</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["- "Surely you have considered terrorist activity?"
There was another pause. Then the spokesman said, in the quiet tones of
someone who has had enough and who is going to quit after this and raise
chickens somewhere, "Yes, I suppose we must. All we need to do is find some
terrorists who are capable of taking an entire nuclear reactor out of its
can while it's running and without anyone noticing. It weighs about a
thousand tons and is forty feet high. So they'll be quite *strong*
terrorists. Perhaps you'd like to ring them up, sir, and ask them questions
in that supercilious, accusatory way of yours.""<br><br>The BBC interviews a nuclear spokesperson - Terry Pratchett & Neil Gaiman, Good Omens]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7/12/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29913</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:58:25 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29913</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["1) I have never waved a hankie in anger
2) I do not peronally know any Morris dancers
3) But Morris dancing is kind of funny and weird at the same time."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, alt.fan.pratchett]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7/11/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29912</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:58:25 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29912</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["He nodded to the troll which was employed by the Drum as a splatter
[footnote: Like a bouncer, but trolls use more force]."<br><br>Nobby takes Carrot for a drink in The Mended Drum - Terry Pratchett, Guards! Guards!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7/10/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29911</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 02:58:25 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29911</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["The Monks of Cool, whose tiny and exclusive monastery is hidden in a really
cool and laid-back valley in the lower Ramtops, have a passing-out test for a
novice. He is taken into a room full of all types of clothing and asked: Yo,
my son, which of these is the most stylish thing to wear? And the correct
answer is: Hey, whatever I select."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Lords and Ladies]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7/9/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29910</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 02:58:25 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29910</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["The old shaman said carefully, "You didn't just see two men go through
upside down on a broomstick, shouting and screaming at each other, did
you?" The boy looked at him levelly. "Certainly not," he said. The old man
heaved a sigh of relief. "Thank goodness for that," he said. "Neither did I.""<br><br>Rincewind and Twoflower take up broomstick flying - Terry Pratchett, The Light Fantastic]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>