<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Daily Pratchett</title>
    <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
    <description>A quote from Sir Terry Pratchett every day.</description>
    <atom:link href="http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/website/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1/12/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28094</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 02:39:42 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28094</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["This is very similar to the suggestion put forward by the Quirmian
philosopher Ventre, who said, "Possibly the gods exist, and possibly they
do not. So why not believe in them in any case? If it's all true you'll go
to a lovely place when you die, and if it isn't then you've lost nothing,
right?" When he died he woke up in a circle of gods holding nasty-looking
sticks and one of them said, "We're going to show you what we think of Mr
Clever Dick in these parts...""<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Hogfather]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1/11/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28093</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 02:39:42 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28093</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["My experience in Amsterdam is that cyclists ride  where the hell they
like and aim in a state of rage at all pedestrians while ringing their
bell loudly, the concept of avoiding people being foreign to them.

My dream holiday would be a) a ticket to Amsterdam b) immunity from
prosecution and c) a baseball bat  :-)"<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, alt.fan.pratchett]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1/10/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28092</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 02:39:42 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28092</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["He hated being thought of as one of those people that wore stupid
ornamental armour. It was gilt by association."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Night Watch]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1/9/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28091</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 02:39:42 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28091</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[""That's why it's always worth having a few philosophers around the place.
One minute it's all Is Truth Beauty and Is Beauty Truth, and Does A Falling
Tree in the Forest Make A Sound if There's No one There to Hear It, and
then just when you think they're going to start dribbling one of 'em says,
Incidentally, putting a thirty-foot parabolic reflector on a high place to
shoot the rays of the sun at an enemy's ships would be a very interesting
demonstration of optical principles.""<br><br>The many and varied advantages of philosophy - Terry Pratchett, Small Gods]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1/8/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28090</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 02:39:42 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=28090</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["A good plan isn't one where someone wins, it's where nobody thinks
they've *lost*."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, The Amazing Maurice and his Educated Rodents]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>