<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Daily Pratchett</title>
    <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
    <description>A quote from Sir Terry Pratchett every day.</description>
    <atom:link href="http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/website/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>7/15/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29934</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 02:59:56 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29934</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["On nights such as these the gods, as has already been pointed out, play
games other than chess with the fates of mortals and the thrones of kings.
It is important to remember that they always cheat, right up to the end..."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Wyrd Sisters]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7/14/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29933</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 02:59:56 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29933</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["It's a metaphor of human bloody existence, a dragon. And if that wasn't bad
enough, it's also a bloody great hot flying thing."<br><br>Captain Vimes ponders his problems - Terry Pratchett, Guards! Guards!]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7/13/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29932</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 02:59:56 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29932</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["- "Surely you have considered terrorist activity?"
There was another pause. Then the spokesman said, in the quiet tones of
someone who has had enough and who is going to quit after this and raise
chickens somewhere, "Yes, I suppose we must. All we need to do is find some
terrorists who are capable of taking an entire nuclear reactor out of its
can while it's running and without anyone noticing. It weighs about a
thousand tons and is forty feet high. So they'll be quite *strong*
terrorists. Perhaps you'd like to ring them up, sir, and ask them questions
in that supercilious, accusatory way of yours.""<br><br>The BBC interviews a nuclear spokesperson - Terry Pratchett & Neil Gaiman, Good Omens]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7/12/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29931</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 02:59:56 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29931</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["1) I have never waved a hankie in anger
2) I do not peronally know any Morris dancers
3) But Morris dancing is kind of funny and weird at the same time."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, alt.fan.pratchett]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>7/11/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29930</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 02:59:56 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=29930</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["He nodded to the troll which was employed by the Drum as a splatter
[footnote: Like a bouncer, but trolls use more force]."<br><br>Nobby takes Carrot for a drink in The Mended Drum - Terry Pratchett, Guards! Guards!]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>