<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Daily Pratchett</title>
    <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
    <description>A quote from Sir Terry Pratchett every day.</description>
    <atom:link href="http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/website/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>9/4/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30444</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 02:18:54 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30444</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["...He hated the very idea of the world being divided into the shaved and
the shavers. Or those who wore the shiny boots and those who cleaned the
mud off them. Every time he saw Willikins the butler fold his, Vimes's,
clothes, he suppressed a terrible urge to kick the butler's shiny backside
as an affront to the dignity of man."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Feet of Clay]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9/3/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30443</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 02:18:54 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30443</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["Many phenomena - wars, plagues, sudden audits - have been advanced as
evidence for the hidden hand of Satan in the affairs of Man, but whenever
students of demonology get together the M25 London orbital motorway is
generally agreed to be among the top contenders for exhibit A."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett & Neil Gaiman, Good Omens]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9/2/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30442</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 02:18:54 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30442</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["In Reading [England] there is this thing called the IDR, short for "Inner
Distribution Road", which is bureaucratese for "Big thing that cost a lot
of money and relieves traffic problems, provided all your traffic wants to
orbit the town centre permanently". It's a 2-3 lane dual carriageway that
goes round the town centre. It has lots of roundabouts, an overhead
section, a couple of spare motorway-like exits (that's British motorways --
y'know, the roundabout with the main road going under it), and a thing
called the Watlington Street Gyratory, where you have to get in lane for
your intended destination about three years and two corners before you get
there *with no signposting*. I used to cycle along it every day to get to
school, before I fell off at 35 mph. [Kids! Don't try this at home!]  I
know it well. I believe it is impossible to leave Reading heading west."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, alt.fan.pratchett]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9/1/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30441</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 02:18:54 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30441</guid>
      <description><![CDATA[""Chap with a whip got as far as the big sharp spikes last week," said
the low priest."<br><br>Life in the Temple of Offler - Terry Pratchett, Reaper Man]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8/31/23</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30440</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 02:18:54 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=30440</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU, he said, BUT I COULD MURDER A CURRY."<br><br>Death addresses his new apprentice - Terry Pratchett, Mort]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>