<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <item>
      <title>2015-05-02</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>The chieftain had been turned into a pumpkin although, in accordance with
the rules of universal humour, he still had his hat on.

 - Terry Pratchett, Lords and Ladies</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-05-01</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>Every procedure for getting a cat to take a pill works fine -- once.
Like the Borg, they learn...

 - Terry Pratchett, alt.fan.pratchett</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-30</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>Everything starts somewhere, though many physicists disagree. But people
have always been dimly aware of the problem with the start of things. They
wonder how the snowplough driver gets to work, or how the makers of
dictionaries look up the spelling of words.

 - Terry Pratchett, Hogfather</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-29</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>Of course, just because we've heard a spine-chilling, blood-curdling
scream of the sort to make your very marrow freeze in your bones doesn't
automatically mean there's anything wrong.

 - Terry Pratchett, Soul Music</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-28</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>...He hated the very idea of the world being divided into the shaved and
the shavers. Or those who wore the shiny boots and those who cleaned the
mud off them. Every time he saw Willikins the butler fold his, Vimes's,
clothes, he suppressed a terrible urge to kick the butler's shiny backside
as an affront to the dignity of man.

 - Terry Pratchett, Feet of Clay</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-27</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>Carrot was two metres tall but he'd been brought up as a dwarf, and then
further up as a human.

 - Terry Pratchett, Men at Arms</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-26</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>Don't put your trust in revolutions. They always come around again.
That's why they're called revolutions. People die, and nothing changes.

 - Terry Pratchett, Night Watch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-25</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>"Eureka," he said.
"Going to have a bath then?"

Philosophy in action - Terry Pratchett, Small Gods</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-24</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>Madame Tracy had even removed most of the Major Arcana from her Tarot card
pack, because their appearance tended to upset people.

 - Terry Pratchett &amp; Neil Gaiman, Good Omens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-23</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>He's going to go totally Librarian-poo.

Gaspode about Vimes - Terry Pratchett, The Truth</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-22</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>Crowley had been extremely impressed with the warranties offered by the
computer industry, and had in fact sent a bundle Below to the department
that drew up the Immortal Soul agreements, with a yellow memo form attached
just saying: "Learn, guys."

Crowley is a demon, in case you don't know - Terry Pratchett &amp; Neil Gaiman, Good Omens</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-21</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>"Students made it long ago," said Rincewind. "Handy way in and out after
lights out."
"Ah," said Twoflower, "I *understand*. Over the wall and out to
brightly-lit tavernas to drink and sing and recite poetry, yes?"
"Nearly right except for the singings and the poetry, yes," said Rincewind.

 - Terry Pratchett, The Light Fantastic</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2015-04-20</title>
      <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
      <description>I didn't go to university. Didn't even finish A-levels. But I have sympathy
for those who did.

 - Terry Pratchett, alt.fan.pratchett</description>
    </item>
    <title>The Daily Pratchett</title>
    <link>http://rolieolie.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
    <description>A quote from Sir Terry Pratchett every day.</description>
  </channel>
</rss>