<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Daily Pratchett</title>
    <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/</link>
    <description>A quote from Sir Terry Pratchett every day.</description>
    <atom:link href="http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/website/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>8/7/22</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26514</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 03:22:20 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26514</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["It would be nice to say that the tiny frogs thought long and hard about the
new flower, about life in the old flower, about the need to explore, about
the possibility that the world was bigger than a pool with petals around
the edge.
In fact, what they thought was: "._._.mipmip._._.mipmip._._.mipmip"."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Wings]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8/6/22</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26513</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 03:22:20 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26513</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["*Glingleglingleglingle.*"<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Hogfather]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8/5/22</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26512</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 03:22:20 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26512</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["There should be a notice ahead of the movie that says 'This
movie is PG.  Can you read?  You are a Parent.  Do you understand what
Guidance is?  Or are you just another stupid toddler who thinks they're
an adult simple because they've grown older and, unfortunately, have
developed fully-functioning sexual organs?  Would you like some
committee somewhere to decide *everything* for you?  Get a damn grip,
will you?  And shut the wretched kid up !'"<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, alt.fan.pratchett]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8/4/22</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26511</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 03:22:20 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26511</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["The librarian was, ex officio, a member of the college council. No-one had
been able to find any rule about orang-utans being barred, although they
had surreptiously looked very hard for one."<br><br>Unseen University politics at work - Terry Pratchett, Eric]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>8/3/22</title>
      <link>http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26510</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 03:22:20 UT</pubDate>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mnocon.github.io/TheDailyPratchett/?id=26510</guid>
      <description><![CDATA["The only things known to go faster than ordinary light is monarchy,
according to the philosopher Ly Tin Weedle. He reasoned like this: you
can't have more than one king, and tradition demands that there is no gap
between kings, so when a king dies the succession must therefore pass to
the heir *instantaneously*. Presumably, he said, there must be some
elementary particles -- kingons, or possibly queons -- that do this job,
but of course succession sometimes fails if, in mid-flight, they strike an
anti-particle, or republicon. His ambitious plans to use his discovery to
send messages, involving the careful torturing of a small king in order to
modulate the signal, were never fully expanded because, at that point, the
bar closed."<br><br> - Terry Pratchett, Mort]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>